<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on vacode</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on vacode</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 20:40:35 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Log</title>
      <link>/log/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 20:40:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/log/</guid>
      <description>[18/04] This page gets updated regularly and my this month&amp;rsquo;s aim is to,
 Complete Sheety Bots Project   Messaging Bot Flow Telegram Notification Bot Flow Use it for a week personally Create a short video and post it on producthunt Complete website and write detailed blog post.  Solve 30 questions in data structure and algorithms ranging in different topics.   Complete 3 questions in Stacks and Queues Complete 4 questions in Stacks and Queues Complete 3 questions in Trees Complete 4 questions in Trees Complete 5 questions in Binary Search Tree Complete 5 questions in Binary Search Trees Complete 3 questions in Binary Trees  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL , ReactJS and Apollo Client</title>
      <link>/2020/06/graphql-reactjs-and-apollo-client_8.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:01:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/06/graphql-reactjs-and-apollo-client_8.html</guid>
      <description>We will build a client-sided GraphQL application which will combine React with GraphQL. The application would allow us to gather facebook profile information
The following tutorial will be split into four sections.
 What is GraphQL and how is it different from REST API. What is Reactjs and Why should you use it? Creating a GraphQL backend in nodejs and express. Connecting Apollo Client to a react application  What is GraphQL and how is it different from REST API?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your First SPA in ReactJS, NodeJS</title>
      <link>/2020/05/your-first-spa-in-reactjs-nodejs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 04:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/05/your-first-spa-in-reactjs-nodejs.html</guid>
      <description>Your First SPA in ReactJs, NodeJS Today we are going to build a simple blog application that will help you get started with ReactJS with back-end built over NodeJS The complete tutorial has been split into SIX IMPORTANT steps.
  Installing the required tools
  Understanding NodeJS structure (Back-end of your application)
  Coding Your APIs
  Understanding ReactJS structure (Front-end of your application)
  Designing and Coding your Front-end</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purists, Makers and Managers</title>
      <link>/2019/09/purists-maker-and-manager.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 18:24:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/09/purists-maker-and-manager.html</guid>
      <description>Whenever I hear the word Purists, I imagine John Nash working hard on his dorm room window sill or Ramanujan relentlessly scribbling on his notepad outside his scabby hut in Erode. I study in a pure science branch and the majority of interested folks tend to have a huge admiration towards the intellectual capital. Often academia and pure science seem to be filled with folks who enjoy making interrogative intonation in declarative sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship after graduation?</title>
      <link>/2017/03/why-entrepreneurship-is-best-way-to-go.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 16:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/why-entrepreneurship-is-best-way-to-go.html</guid>
      <description>A lot of my friends are in computer science and there are a lot of them who are not but want to learn programming and get into software development so that they can hack the plethora of high paying white collar jobs out there. The government and and the industry seems to be happy about it and are fueling this environment with more venture fund and government funds. Sure, the number of different applications in which software can easily and dramatically increase productivity is practically unlimited, so each additional worker in the tech industry always has important problems to solve, and the other software engineers are occupied with their own problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>